-= CHD字幕組 原創翻譯 =-
字幕僅供翻譯學習交流 謝絕用於任何商業用途
翻譯：貓妖先生@CHDBits
校對：貓妖先生@CHDBits
一想起來就嚇人
It scares us just thinking about it.
你們會覺得我們瘋了的
When you hear it, you're gonna think we're insane.
說來聽聽，從頭開始
Try us. Please, from the start.
一開始沒什麼，只是手腳在不同位置而已
It started out small,like a hand or a leg was in a different position.
然後它的腦袋變成了向上，而不是向下
Then its head was looking up instead of down.
然後有一天，它突然出現在另一個房間
And then one day, it was in a completely different room.
它會自己挪地方
It was moving around by itself.
是不是有人有你公寓的鑰匙，跟你惡作劇？
Ever think maybe somebody had a key to your apartment and was playing a trick on you?
我們也這麼想過
That's exactly what we thought.
但沒有發現任何有人進來過的痕跡
But never once did we find any sign or evidence of intrusion.
(安娜貝爾事件 - 1968年)
所以你們認為這個娃娃是被附身了？
And this all led you to believe that the doll was possessed?
是的
Yes.
卡米拉聯繫過一位靈媒，她說有個名叫安娜貝爾·希金斯…
Camilla got in touch with a medium.We learned from her that a 7-year-old girl...
…的7歲小女孩曾經死在這個公寓裏
...named Annabelle Higgins had died in this apartment.
她很孤獨並且很喜歡我的娃娃
She was lonely and took a liking to my doll.
她只想要交朋友
All she wanted was to be friends.
我們知道這些後覺得她很可憐
When we heard this,we felt really sorry for her.
我們是護士，幫助人是我們的職責
I mean, we're nurses, we help people.
然後…
So...
…我們允許她進入了那個娃娃
...we gave her permission to move into the doll.
等等，你們做了什麼？
Wait, you did what?
她想附身在娃娃裏跟我們一起生活
She wanted to live with us by inhabiting the doll.
我們同意了
We said yes.
然後情況越來越糟
But then things got worse.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
(想我嗎？)
上帝啊
God.
我們回家的時候，她坐在走廊上
When we came home,she was sitting in the hallway.
但我們走的時候是把她放在空房間裏的
But we had left her in the spare room.
黛比！黛比，等我！
Debbie! Debbie, wait!
我們嚇壞了
We are beyond terrified.
不知道怎麼回事、該怎麼做，可以幫幫我們嗎？
We don't know what's going on or what to do. Can you help us?
可以
Yes, we can.
首先，安娜貝爾並不存在，從來沒有
Now, firstly, there's no such thing as Annabelle, and there never was.
鬼魂沒有如此強大的力量
Ghosts don't possess such power.
我認為我們面對的是某種非常有心計
I think what we have here is something extremely manipulative.
某種兇殘的東西
It's something inhuman.
你們對這娃娃的認識是非常錯誤的
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.
這樣看來，是這個惡靈算計了你們
And through that,the inhuman spirit tricked you.
你們給了它侵擾你們生命的許可
You gave it permission to infest your lives.
什麼是惡靈？
What's an inhuman spirit?
某種從未以人類形態出現過的
It's something that's never walked the earth in human form.
邪惡的東西
It's something demonic.
所以娃娃並沒有被附身？
So the doll was never possessed?
不，不，這只是它的載體
No, no, it was used as a conduit.
它自己挪動位置，讓人覺得是被附身了
It was moved around to give the impression of possession.
惡靈不會附身於物品，它們只會附身於人類
Demonic spirits don't possess things,they possess people.
它想佔有你們的身體
It wanted to get inside of you.
很好，德魯，可以關掉了
All right, that's good, Drew.You can shut it down now.
開燈
Hit the lights.
所以我們讓教堂派了一位牧師過去
So we got the church to send a priest over...
給那房子以及住客進行了一次賜福
...to perform a blessing on the house and the occupants.
困擾那公寓的東西已經沒有了，還有什麼問題嗎？
Whatever was oppressing that apartment was no longer with them. Any questions?
你
Yes.
那娃娃現在在哪？
Where's the doll now?
某個安全的地方
Someplace safe.
你  - 你們什麼人？
Yep.  - So, what are you guys?
我是說，別人怎麼稱呼你們？
I mean, what do people call you?
嗯，好吧，有人稱呼我們為「神鬼學家」
Uh, well, we've been called Demonologists.That's one name for us.
「獵魔人」，「靈異研究者」
Ghost hunters, paranormal researchers.
「怪人」
Kooks.
「瘋子」
Wackos.
但我們更想被叫做「艾德和羅琳·沃倫」
But we prefer to be known simply as Ed and Lorraine Warren.
1960年起，艾德和羅琳·沃倫被認為是世上最著名的靈異現象調查者
羅琳擁有陰陽眼，艾德是天主教會唯一認可的神鬼學家
他們飽受爭議的事業中經歷了無數事件
唯有一件極度邪惡的事件，直到現在才為人所知
基於真實故事改編
《招魂》
1971年，哈瑞斯維爾，羅德島
我們到了
Here we are.
哇噢，聽到了嗎？
Wow, hear that?
我什麼都沒聽到  - 沒錯
I don't hear anything.  - Exactly.
好吧！
Oh. Okay!
好了，孩子們，我們到了！下車
Okay. Guys, we are here!Get out of the car.
上帝啊，我們在荒郊野外
Oh, God, we're in the middle of nowhere.
你們激動嗎？給我個肯定的回答，是的！
Are you so excited?Where's my "yes"? Where's my "yes"? Yes!
比誰跑得快
I'll race you!
你們激動嗎？  - 是的！
Are you guys excited?  - Yes!
我很激動！  - 快來，賽迪！
I'm so excited!  - Come on, Sadie!
我自己選房間！
I get my own room!
你開玩笑吧？不准挑房間！
Are you kidding me?No dibs on the rooms!
什麼？  - 什麼？
What?  - What?
那我可以自己選房間嗎？還是也一樣沒得選？
So do I get to pick my own room?Or do I have no choice in that either?
她遇到心儀的男孩就會忘了新澤西的
Well, first cute boy she meets,she'll forget about Jersey.
很好  - 但願
Great.  - I hope.
我等不及了
I can't wait.
過來，賽迪
Come on, Sadie.
賽迪，走吧
Sadie, let's go.
過來啊
Hey, come.
你怎麼了？
What's the matter with you?
來啊，小妞
Hey, come on, girl.
好吧，隨你
All right, suit yourself.
小心台階
Watch your step.
借過
Coming through.
哇噢，小心，老爸
Whoa, watch out, Dad.
你想把它放在哪？  - 客廳
Where do you want it?  - In the living room.
安德莉亞，我的風鈴在哪？  - 好像南希拿到另一個房間了
Andrea, where's my wind chime?  - I think Nancy's got it in the other room.
謝了！ 南希，看到我的風鈴了嗎？
Thanks! Hey, Nancy,have you seen my wind chime?
這個嗎？  - 是的，謝謝
Oh, this one?  - Yeah, thanks.
自己來拿  - 南希！放手！給我
You're gonna have to catch it.  - Nancy! Let go! Give it here.
你太壞了
You're so mean.
媽媽，我可以掛風鈴嗎？
Hey, Mom, can I hang up my wind chime?
當然，外面有條繩子，你可以掛在那
Of course. There's a line outside you can hang it on.
親愛的，把艾普麗爾叫進來好嗎？天快黑了
Honey, have April come in, okay?It's gonna be dark soon.
好的
Okay.
過來，艾普麗爾！媽媽讓我們進屋
Come on, April! Mom wants us inside!
看我找到了什麼，辛蒂
Look what I found, Cindy.
一
One...
二
...two...
三
...three.
快，快，快，不准偷看
Come on, come on, come on.No peeking.
四
Four.
披薩吃完了嗎？我不希望浪費
Are you guys done with the pizza?I don't want it going to waste.
快走  - 養你們這群小丫頭很費錢啊
Let's go.  - It's expensive feeding you girls.
七，八，九
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
我該躲哪裏？
Where should I hide?
準備好了嗎，我來了！
Ready or not, here I come!
好，拍手
Okay, clap.
哇噢！  - 你們對這屋子還不熟悉
Whoa!  - Guys,You don't know the house well enough.
有人會受傷的
Someone's gonna get hurt.
我沒事，我沒事
I'm okay, I'm okay.
拍第二次
Second clap.
這是作弊
That's cheating.
拍手
Clap.
抓住你了！
Got you!
你沒事吧？  - 還好
Are you okay?  - Um,Yeah.
弄壞了什麼東西？
All right, what did we break now?
我不是故意的  - 麻煩請出來
I didn't mean to.  - Move out of there, please.
是克裏斯蒂的錯
It was Christine's fault.
老天  - 我的錯？上帝啊
Oh, jeez.  - My fault? Oh, my God.
是克裏斯蒂干的  - 不，我沒有
Christine did it.  - No, I didn't.
你推我的  - 不，不，你自己退過去的
You pushed me.  - No, no, you fell back.
南希，幫我拿一下火柴，好嗎？
Hey, Nancy, can you go get me the matches, please?
怎麼了？
What's going on?
南希弄壞東西了  - 閉嘴
Nancy broke something.  - Shut up.
是你！
It was you!
什麼壞了？  - 是牆
What broke?  - It's the wall.
哇噢！  - 我覺得好像是個地下室什麼的
Whoa!  - I think we have a cellar or something.
我要看，我要看，讓開，讓開，讓開
I wanna see, I wanna see. Move, move, move.
來，火柴，謝謝
Here, matches.Thank you.
我要看  - 你會看到的
I wanna see.  - You can see.
我要看嘛  - 你們都會看到的
I wanna see.  - You can all see.
走開！
Move!
天
Oh, man.
羅傑？
Roger?
下面有什麼？
What do you see down there?
只是…呃，很難解釋
Just, uh, hard to tell, you know?
一架舊鋼琴，還有一堆垃圾
It's an old piano and a whole bunch of garbage.
啊，媽的…
Ah. Son of a...
哇噢
Wow.
羅傑？
Roger?
上來吧
Come on up.
我不希望你們下去那裏
I don't want you girls going down there.
那裏都是蜘蛛  - 嘔！
That place is loaded with spiders.  - Ew!
別緊張
Just relax.
別這樣，南希，這不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny.
不管怎麼說，我們有更多空間了，明早我再下去看看
We've got extra square footage anyway.I'll check it out in the morning.
我在想為什麼要封起來  - 不知道
I wonder why it was boarded up.  - I don't know.
好了，孩子們，演出結束
Okay,guys.Show's over.
再五分鐘  - 一分都不行
Five minutes.  - No more minutes.
趕緊上床，謝謝合作  - 上床
Up to bed. Please. Thank you.  - Right to bed.
累死了
Man, I'm fried.
賽迪有點不對勁
Something's up with Sadie.
是啊，不知道她怎麼了，就是不肯進來
Yeah, I don't know what her problem is.Couldn't get her to come inside.
我們不能把她扔在那
We can't leave her out there.
沒事的，我把她拴鏈子上了
She's all right. I got her on a chain.
賽迪，安靜點
Sadie, hey, be quiet.
謝謝把這一切變為可能
Thanks for making this work.
我知道還有很多事要做
I know it was a lot to bite off.
會好起來，對嗎？
It's gonna be great, isn't it?
我覺得已經很好了
I think it's great already.
是啊
Yeah.
你還累的無法打理新房子嗎？
You still too fried to christen the new house?
誰說我累壞了？
Who said I'm fried?
誰都沒有累壞
Ain't nobody here's fried.
媽媽？
Mom?
嗨，你們睡的還好嗎？
Hey. How did you guys sleep?
我好冷
I'm cold.
的確有點涼
It is chilly, isn't it?
我們可以買一棟廁所實際可用的房子嗎？
Do you think maybe we could have bought a house with a toilet that actually works?
跟你爸說去
Tell your father.
昨晚我房間裏還有股怪味，好像什麼東西死了一樣
And there was a funky smell in my room last night. Like something died.
現在還有嗎？  - 沒了
Is it still there?  - No.
那就沒問題了
Problem solved.
羅傑？
Roger?
在下面，親愛的
Down here, honey.
早上好
Morning.
這可真得花一番大工夫了
This is gonna take some serious elbow grease.
是啊
Yeah.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
這些東西該怎麼處理？
What are we gonna do with all this stuff?
或許我們該先整理一下
Well, we probably ought to go through it
知道嗎？可能有些很值錢的古董
You know?There might be some antiques down here worth a lot of  money.
或者只是一堆前任房主不要的廢物
Yeah, or just a lot of junk the previous owner didn't want.
現在是我們的了  - 別做夢了
It's ours now.  - Knock yourself out.
我去煮點咖啡  - 好的
I'm gonna make some coffee.  - Okay.
我很快就上來，我要試試能否把這爐子修好
I'll be up in a minute,I'm gonna see if I can get this furnace working.
那就太好了，這裏冷死了
Yeah, that'd be nice. It's freezing.
是啊
Yeah.
賽迪！來這裏，賽迪！
Sadie! Come here, Sadie!
媽咪！
Mommy!
媽咪，賽迪在哪？
Mommy, where's Sadie?
她在外面，她現在一定很餓了，你去把她帶過來吧
She's outside. You know, I'm sure she's hungry by now. Why don't you go and get her.
早上好，爸爸
Morning, Dad.
可以幫我拿一下嗎？  - 當然
Can you hold this?  - Sure.
賽迪！  - 慢點，小皮猴
Sadie!  - Slow it down, Scoot.
羅傑  - 怎麼
Roger.  - Yeah.
這鍾停在了3:07，走廊那個也是
This clock stopped at 3:07,and so did the one in the hallway.
這倒挺奇怪的
That's weird.
可能是搬家的時候撞壞了吧
Maybe it got knocked around in the move.
說到撞壞，你昨晚對我做了什麼？
Speaking of knocked around,what did you do to me last night?
這不是我幹的，是我弄的嗎？  - 我不知道
Ouch. I didn't do that. Did I?  - I don't know.
賽迪！
Sadie!
艾普麗爾！艾普麗爾！
April! April!
怎麼…？艾普麗爾！發生什麼事了？
What's...? April! What's going on?
怎麼了？  - 上帝啊！
What happened?  - Oh, my God!
噢，賽迪
Oh, Sadie.
門羅，康乃狄克州，沃倫家
我們把所有東西都鎖在這裏了
We keep everything locked in here.
請隨便參觀
Feel free to look around.
就是別碰任何東西
Just don't touch anything.
哇噢
Wow.
太瘋狂了
This is crazy.
這些都是從你們調查的案子中得來的嗎？
So all these are taken from cases you've investigated?
是的，你所看到的一切，不是被詛咒的…
That's right. Everything you see in here is either haunted, cursed...
…就是曾被用於某種儀式的器物
...or has been used in some kind of ritualistic practice.
沒有一樣是玩具
Nothing's a toy.
甚至是那個玩具猴子
Not even the toy monkey.
別碰
Don't touch it.
好吧，是這些不可怕，還是你一點都不擔心…
Oh,  Well, isn't it scary,or doesn't it worry you...
把這些東西放在家裏？
...to have all these items right in your home?
所以我們才讓牧師每個月來這房間賜福一次
That's why we have a priest that comes by once a month to bless the room.
我覺得…
Well, the way I see it is...
這些東西放這裏比放在別的地方更安全
It's safer for these things to be in here than out there.
就跟不把槍帶上街一個道理
It's kind of like keeping guns off the street.
為什麼不把這些扔進焚化爐銷毀掉？
Why not just throw them in an incinerator? Destroy them.
那樣只是毀了它們的皮囊
Well, that would only destroy the vessel.
還是把妖怪封在瓶子裏更好
Sometimes it's better to keep the genie in the bottle.
說起來，安娜貝爾娃娃在這裏嗎？
Say, is the, uh, Annabelle doll here?
這邊走
Right this way.
好的
Yeah.
你說她只是個載體？  - 正確
You said she's a conduit?  - That's right.
那是什麼意思？
What does that mean?
一個非常強大的惡魔把自己附著在她身上
A very powerful demonic has latched itself onto her.
那當你們在調查這些事件的時候…
So when you guys investigate these hauntings...
…是如何避免被他們纏上的呢？
...how do you stop them from latching onto you?
我們會做好一切預防措施
We have to take great precaution.
那你妻子呢？
But what about your wife?
她怎麼了？
What about her?
哥頓神父告訴我…
Well, Father Gordon told me that...
那是不一樣的
Well, that was different.
驅魔的時經常會有這樣的事情發生
What happened to my wife happened during an exorcism.
有什麼區別？
Well, what's the difference?
抱歉
Excuse me.
親愛的，你在幹嗎？
Honey, what are you doing?
過來
Come here.
你更瞭解，是嗎？
You know better. All right?
喬治安娜？
Georgiana?
你碰過什麼東西嗎？  - 沒有
Come on. Did you touch anything?  - No.
好的，過來，親愛的
All right, come on, honey.
喬治安娜！把朱蒂帶上樓好嗎？  - 噢，當然
Georgiana! Could you take Judy upstairs?  - Oh, sure.
無論如何你都不能進那間房間，還記得嗎？
You can't go into this room,no matter what, remember?
是的，爸爸  - 好的
Yes, Daddy.  - All right.
去吧  - 好的，過來
Go on.  - Okay, come on.
我去給你找點零食，好嗎？來吧
Let's see if I can find you a little snack, okay? Come on.
你們在做什麼？
Hey. What's going on in here?
爸爸，看  - 你真漂亮
Daddy, look.  - You look very pretty.
好了，完成了，穿好衣服吃飯去
All right, all done.Go get dressed for dinner.
我就穿這個去吃飯  - 不，不行
I'm wearing it to dinner.  - No, you're not!
給你
Here you go.
怎麼樣了？
How'd it go?
我覺得他或許是想寫一篇正面報道
Oh, I think he may write a positive article.
噢，一個有神論者
Ooh, a non-skeptic.
這是個不錯的改變
That's a pleasant change.
是的
Yeah.
別再自責了
Stop blaming yourself.
沒放糖
No sugar.
很快回來
Be right back.
這不好玩，南希
Not funny, Nancy.
什麼？
What?
別抓我的腳
Stop grabbing my foot.
閉嘴，我什麼都沒做
Shut up, I didn't do anything.
是啊，是啊
Yeah, right.
別再放屁了
And stop farting.
真的很臭
It really stinks.
別怪我頭上，是你自己
Don't blame that on me. It's you.
老爸？
Dad?
安德莉亞，為什麼不睡覺？
Andrea, what are you doing out of bed?
那是什麼聲音？
What's that sound?
是辛蒂，她在我房間，她又夢遊了
It's Cindy. She's in my room.She's sleepwalking again.
我從沒見過她這樣子
I've never seen her do this before.
我記得你說夢遊的時候不要吵醒她
I remembered you saying not to wake her if she's like this.
是的，我們把她放回床裏
No, we just put her back to bed.
嗨，嗨，寶貝，噓
Hey, hey. Sweetie. Shh.
我們回床裏去
Let's go back to bed.
她沒事了，晚安
She's okay. Good night.
晚安
Night.
她又夢遊了？好久都沒這樣過了
She's sleepwalking again?She hasn't done that for awhile.
她停在了安德莉亞的房間裏，嚇壞她了
She ended up in Andrea's room too.I think kind of freaked her out.
這不太妙，我們該怎麼做？  - 不知道
That's not good. What are we gonna do?  - I don't know.
親愛的，這裏又有一塊淤青了  - 嗯？
Honey, you got another bruise here.  - Hmm?
疼嗎？
Does that hurt?
真奇怪
That's weird.
我不知道，要不要去看一下醫生？
I don't know. Will you do me a favor,go see a doctor for that?
好，我會的，開車小心  - 知道了
Yeah, I will. Drive safe.  - Yeah.
我愛你  - 我也愛你
I love you.  - I love you too.
再見！
Bye!
愛你們！
Love you!
辛蒂，拿午餐了嗎？  - 拿了
Cindy, you have your lunch?  - Yeah.
是的
Yes, I do.
我很想賽迪
I miss Sadie a lot.
她是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend.
你是我的朋友，對嗎？
You're my friend, right?
好的，我們一起玩吧
Yeah, let's play.
你在跟誰說話？  - 羅利
Who are you talking to?  - Rory.
羅利？
Rory?
他是我的新朋友  - 噢，是嗎？
He's my new friend.  - Oh, really?
是的，你想見他嗎？  - 好啊，怎麼見？
Yeah, do you want to see him?  - Yeah. Uh-huh. How?
用這個
With this.
當音樂停的時候，你會看到他在鏡子裏，站在你身後
When the music stops, you see him in the mirror standing behind you.
好吧
Okay.
但你得擰發條
But you have to twist the key.
好的
Okay.
砰！媽咪！  - 噢！
Boo, Mommy!  - Oh!
艾普麗爾，你嚇死我了  - 中招！
April, you just gave me a heart attack.  - Got you!
好吧，我猜羅利不想見我，是嗎？
Well, okay, I guess Rory doesn't want to see me, huh?
噢，好吧
Oh, well.
我們可以玩捉迷藏嗎？
Can we play hide-and-clap?
捉迷…？噢，親愛的，我不想玩
Hide-and-cla--?Oh, honey, I don't want to play.
求你！她們都不讓我玩  - 好吧，好吧
Please! Nobody ever lets me play.  - Okay, okay.
記住，你得要求我拍三次手
Remember, you get to ask me for three claps.
好的
Okay.
一，二，三
One, two, three.
我要躲起來了！  - 好的
I'm gonna go hide now!  - Okay.
四，五…
Four, five...
六，七…
...six, seven...
八，九…
...eight, nine...
十！
...ten!
拍第一次手！
First clap!
噢，該死
Ow. Shit.
拍第二次手！
Second clap!
艾普麗爾
April.
我知道你藏在哪裏
Oh, I know where you're hiding.
拍第三次手
Give me the third clap.
我要把你抓出來嘍
I'm gonna get you now.
我聽到你呼吸了
I can hear you breathing.
艾普麗爾
April.
你把眼罩拿下來了，我贏了！
You took your blindfold off. I win!
你一點都不用心，媽媽，我在克裏斯蒂跟南希的房間
You weren't even warm, Mom.I was in Christine and Nancy's room.
總得給我留一條路線，不然我會失去卡車保險的
I gotta have some routes here,or I'm gonna lose the insurance on the rig.
這才只有半價啊，兄弟
That's like half of my rate, man.
嗯，好的
Yeah, okay.
我…好吧，我接下了
I'll, uh... Yeah, I'll take it.
謝謝
Thank you.
什麼路線？  - 是…佛羅里達
What's the route?  - It's, uh, Florida.
往返一個星期，我明天出發
It's a week turnaround. I start tomorrow.
我們會撐過去的
We'll get through this.
是的
Yeah.
來，去睡覺吧
Come on, let's go to bed.
住手，南希，這一點都不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny anymore.
我要睡覺，求你別再抓我的腳了
I'm trying to sleep,please stop grabbing my feet.
南希？
Nancy?
你在幹嗎？
What are you doing?
克裏斯蒂？
Christine?
你還好嗎？
Are you all right?
你看到了嗎？
Do you see it?
看到什麼？
See what?
有人在門後
There's someone behind the door.
什麼？
What?
有個人站在那裏
There's someone standing over there.
我沒看到任何人
I don't see anyone.
它正看著我們
It's looking right at us.
南希，不要！南希
Nancy, don't! Nancy.
不，不，你看，你看
No, no. Look. Look.
看，沒有人，看到了嗎？
Look, there's no one...no one here. See?
又是那味道
Ugh. It's that smell again.
噢，上帝啊
Oh, my God.
它就站在你背後
It's standing right behind you.
克裏斯蒂？！克裏斯蒂！克裏斯蒂！
Christine?! Christine! Christine!
天，開不了…
God, it won't op...
克裏斯蒂！  - 不！不！不！
Christine!  - No! No! No!
怎麼了？發生什麼事了？  - 有個人在這裏！
What's going on? What happened?  - There was someone else in here!
什麼？  - 哪裏？
What?  - Where?
門邊，它在門背後
By the door. It was behind the door.
寶貝，什麼都沒有，沒人在那裏
Honey, there's nothing in here.There's nobody in here.
有個人在這裏！
There was someone else in here!
我正在睡覺，然後覺得有人抓著我的腳
I was just sleeping, and then I felt somebody grab my feet.
我以為是南希
So I thought it was Nancy.
寶貝，我非常確定那只是個噩夢
Well, honey, I'm pretty sure that it was just a bad dream.
不是！它跟我說話了！
No! It talked to me!
它說…
It said...
它想要我們全家都死掉
...that it wants my family dead.
溫斯頓先生！
Mr. Winston!
溫斯頓？溫斯頓？
Winston? Winston?
到他後面
Get behind him.
你要去哪？
Where you off to?
打算去店裏買點東西
I just gotta run to the store for a few things.
為什麼要這樣？  - 什麼？什麼意思？
Why do you even try?  - What? What do you mean?
15年來，你有哪次是能騙過我的？
In 15 years have you ever been able to lie to me?
哥頓神父打電話來，說他有個案子想讓我們跟進一下
Father Gordon called. He's got a case he wants us to look into.
我說我會過去看看的，羅琳，是「我」會
I said I'd go check it out myself.Lorraine, myself.
我跟你一起去
I'm going with you.
我知道你擔心那個會再次發生
I know you're worried it's gonna happen again.
是啊，千真萬確
Yeah, I am. I really am.
或許我們該歇一歇了，寫本書什麼的
Maybe it's just time we take a break.Write that book.
還記得結婚那晚你跟我說了什麼嗎？
Do you remember what you said to me on our wedding night?
「能再來一次嗎？」
"Can we do it again?"
在這之後
After that.
你說上帝把我們撮合在一起是有原因的，對嗎？
You said that God brought us together for a reason. Right?
我很確定不是為了寫書什麼的
I'm pretty sure it's not to write a book.
我去穿件衣服
I'm gonna get dressed.
我們已經確定那東西就在這閣樓上
We've isolated the disturbances to the attic.
你們聽
Now I just want you to listen for a second.
噢，上帝啊，就是這個
Oh, my God, that's it.
再來一次，艾德
Do it again, Ed.
現在只是我在踩地板而已，但你們從水管裏放水的時候
Right now it's just my weight.But you take the water coming off the pipe...
會把風從那破窗子裏帶進來
...combined with the wind coming through the broken window...
然後這些木條就會脹大，互相摩擦
...these boards are gonna expand and rub against each other.
滿屋子都有這聲音，是因為這些管子是連著暖氣片的
You heard it all through the house because of these pipes leading to the radiator.
所以這地方並沒有鬧鬼？
So this place isn't haunted?
是的，不太可能
No, it rarely is.
有時候的確是可以有合理解釋的
Yeah, there's usually always some kind of rational explanation.
丫頭們，該睡覺了
Girls, it's way past your bedtime.
是誰？
Who is that?
誰在下面，我要把你關起來了
Who's ever down there,I'm gonna lock you in now!
救命！
Help!
安德莉亞，救命！
Andrea! Help!
嗨，想玩捉迷藏嗎？
Hey, wanna play hide-and-clap?
辛蒂？
Cindy?
好吧，那…
Okay, now....
是這樣嗎？
All right?
沒錯，過來
All right, come on.
過來
Come on.
就這樣
There you go.
好了，今晚就跟我一起睡了，好嗎？
Okay, you can just sleep with me tonight,all right?
來
There you go.
對了
There.
安德莉亞？  - 救命！救命！救命！
Andrea?  - Help! Help! Help!
誰在裏面？  - 安德莉亞？
Who's in here?  - Andrea!
安德莉亞？安德莉亞！
Andrea? Andrea!
在這裏！
In here!
救命，爸爸！救命，是安德莉亞！
Help, Daddy! Help, it's Andrea!
誰在這裏？  - 安德莉亞！
Who's in here?  - Andrea!
發生什麼事了？
What happened?
該死的，誰能告訴我這裏發生了什麼事？
Somebody, goddamn it,tell me what's going on here?
恐懼就是，未知事物或強烈危機感所致的…
Fear is defined as a feeling of agitation and anxiety caused by the presence...
情緒波動及焦慮
...or imminence of danger.
無論是鬼魂、妖魔還是邪物，都以此為生
Whether it's a ghost, a spirit or an entity, they all feed on it.
(馬薩諸塞西部大學，韋克菲爾德)
這是莫裏斯
Take Maurice here.
一個三年級都沒念完的加籍法裔農民
A French-Canadian farmer with no more than a third-grade education...
被附身之後，說著一口我聽過最標準的拉丁語
...yet after he was possessed,spoke some of the best Latin I'd ever heard.
有時還倒過來說
Sometimes backwards.
他一直被他的父親騷擾、折磨著
He'd been molested by his father,who had also tortured him repeatedly.
一個把他當做宿主的暗靈
A dark spirit made its home in this man.
你們看他的眼睛，會發現他在流血淚
Now, if you look into his eyes,you can see him tearing blood.
還有這樣…
And like that...
…從身體裏浮現出一個倒十字架
...an upside-down cross started to appear from within his body.
好，德魯，可以開燈了
All right, Drew, you can hit the lights.
你會親自主持驅魔儀式嗎？
Did you personally perform the exorcism?
不，我沒有被授權，但我協助過很多
No, I'm not authorized.But I've assisted on many.
要知道，驅魔是非常危險的…
See, an exorcism can be very dangerous...
不僅只對受害者而言，對屋裏的所有人都一樣
...not only for the victim,but for anyone in the room.
莫裏斯怎樣了？  - 他試圖殺了他妻子…
What happened to Maurice?  - He tried to kill his wife...
…但只打傷了她的胳膊，然後他把槍對準了自己
...but instead shot her in the arm and then turned the gun on himself.
莫裏斯的生活很悲慘…
Maurice had a very troubled life with little to live for...
…甚至連驅魔都無法救回他
...and not even an exorcist could bring him back.
由此，讓我們看一下惡魔活動的三個階段
Which brings us to the three stages of demonic activity:
出現，騷擾，附身
Infestation, oppression and possession.
首先，「出現」
Now, infestation:
一般就是說話聲、腳步聲以及感覺有另外一個人存在…
That's the whispering, the footsteps,the feeling of another presence...
…很快就會發展成第二階段「騷擾」，
...which ultimately grows into oppression, the second stage.
所以受害者一般都是那些…
Now this is where the victim,and it's usually the one...
…比較容易受外部力量影響的…
...who's the most psychologically vulnerable...
…心理承受能力比較差的人
...is targeted specifically by an external force.
把受害者嚇倒，摧毀他們的意志
Breaks the victim down.Crushes their will.
在他們最脆弱的時候，就發展到了最後也就是第三階段，「附身」
And, once in a weakened state, leads them to the third and final stage: possession.
嗨，艾德？羅琳？  - 是的
Hey, Ed? Lorraine?  - Yeah.
有人想跟你們聊聊
There's someone here that would like to talk to you.
嗨  - 謝謝，德魯
Hi.  - Thanks, Drew.
謝謝  - 沒事，待會兒見
Thank you.  - Sure，I'll see you later.
有什麼可以幫你的？
How can we help you?
我房子裏發生了很可怕的事情，你們可以來看一下嗎？
There's something horrible happening in my house. Could you come and take a look?
嗯…呃…今天有點晚了
You know, uh, it's getting kinda late.
我們要回家了  - 不，你們不明白
We really need to be head to our family.  - No,You don't understand.
事實上我們知道，很多東西是可以有合理解釋的…
But we do. There's usually some sort of rational explanation...
我五個女兒都被嚇壞了，我擔心這東西會傷害我們
I have five daughters who are scared to death.I'm so afraid this thing wants to hurt us.
你們也有女兒，難道你們就不會竭盡所能去保護她嗎？求你們
You have a daughter. Wouldn't you do anything you could to protect her? Please.
求你們來看一下可以嗎？
Please can you come and take a look?
好的，當然
Of course we will.
孩子們，趕緊整理一下，謝謝
Hey,You guys straighten up? Thanks.
你好  - 嗨
Hello. Hi.  - Hi. Hi.
非常感謝能來
Thanks for coming.
你好，我是羅傑  - 羅琳
Hi, I'm Roger.  - Lorraine.
你好，幸會，羅傑，我是艾德·沃倫
Hey, nice to meet you, Roger. Ed Warren.
非常感謝能來  - 請進來吧
Thanks for coming.  - Please, come in.
謝謝
Thank you.
那…
So....
噢，天啊，看看，這些美女們都是誰？
Oh, my God. Look at you all.Who are these beautiful young women?
這是安德莉亞，老大，南希、辛蒂、克裏斯蒂…
This is Andrea, the oldest,Nancy, Cindy, Christine...
…還有艾普麗爾
...and April.
這是沃倫先生和沃倫太太
It's Mr. and Mrs. Warren.
我們現在都睡在樓下
We're all sleeping down here now.
孩子們有點安全感，也更暖和一些
The girls feel safer and it's warmer.
我一直開著暖氣，但這房子就是冷得要命
I'm constantly turning up the heat,but the house is always freezing.
爐子沒什麼問題
It's not a problem with the furnace.
我是說，我找不出原因
I mean, not that I can find.
前幾晚情況越來越糟糕了
It's gotten a lot worse the past few nights.
有股難聞的味道，像爛肉一樣，滿屋子都是
There's this awful smell, like rotting meat.It moves around the house.
呃…
Uh....
什麼？怎麼了？
What? What is it?
腐臭味有可能是某種惡魔活動徵兆
Well, rancid smells could indicate some type of demonic activity.
噢，上帝啊
Oh, my God.
這是為了防止晚上發出碰門聲
That's to keep those doors from banging at night.
不然，整晚都會像這樣響個不停
Otherwise, it's like...All night long, just like that.
每天都會發生？  - 是的
Does it come in threes?  - Yeah.
天亮就停？
It stops at dawn?
對
Uh-huh.
有時這意味著對三聖的不敬
Well, sometimes it's meant as an insult to the Trinity:
聖父、聖子、聖靈
The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
知道嗎，這是非常邪惡的東西，但我們有辦法…
You know, it's the damndest thing,but we also get all kinds of birds...
…可以把它從這房子裏找出來消滅掉
...that will just fly against the side of the house and break their necks.
是嗎？
Hm. Really?
鍾都停在了凌晨3:07
And the clocks stop at 3:07 a.m.
所有的？  - 每個都是
All of them?  - Every one.
噢，這些原本都是掛在樓梯上的
Oh, we were hanging those along the stairs.
有東西老是會把它們弄下來，所以就不掛回去了
Something just kept knocking them down,so we stopped hanging them up.
我一直在說
That's what I was talking about.
我們搬來的時候它就已經在了
It was here when we moved in.
地下室裏還有很多東西
There's also a lot of stuff in the cellar.
帶我去地下室看看
Show me the cellar.
看看她都讓我幹了些什麼
Look what she made me do.
發現什麼了嗎，親愛的？
You picking up anything in here, hon?
這裏發生過很可怕的事情，艾德
Something awful happened here, Ed.
這些淤青，是來這裏之後出現的嗎？
Those bruises, they from something that happened here?
這是因為我身體缺鐵什麼的
Oh, it's some iron deficiency thing I have.
發生了那麼多事，你們為什麼不搬走？
You know, with all that's been going on,why haven't you just moved out?
不知道我們可以搬去哪
I don't know where we'd move to, you know?
我們把所有錢都花在了這裏，還進行了很多整修
We got all our money tied up in this place and had a lot of repairs on top of that.
我也不知道誰可以長期收留我們一家七口人
And I don't know anybody whose gonna take in a family of seven indefinitely.
所以我們找到了你們
That's why we tracked you down.
很榮幸你們能來找我們
We're glad you found us.
好，開始吧
All right, let's get started.
我叫艾德·沃倫，今天是1971年11月1日
My name is Ed Warren.It's November 1st, 1971.
我現在跟卡洛琳·佩倫坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正經歷著靈異事件
...who, with her family, has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，開始吧
Okay, go ahead.
從哪裏說起？
Where do I start?
從初次異常現象開始
From the first occurrence.
我覺得應該是那些鍾
I guess it was the clocks.
爸爸媽媽跟我說你有個朋友
Mom and Dad tell me that you have a friend.
他叫羅利，他也住在這裏
His name's Rory.He lives here too.
嗯  - 但他一直很悲傷
Hmm.  - But he's always sad.
為什麼？
Why is that?
他不告訴我，可能有什麼不好的事情發生在他身上了
He won't tell me but I think something bad happened to him.
可以讓我見見羅利嗎？
Do you mind if I try to see Rory?
嗨
Hey.
怎麼了？
What is it?
我們是從銀行拍賣來的，所以不知道之前誰住在這裏
We bought it at auction from the bank, so,you know, we never knew who lived here.
羅琳跟我都覺得你們的房子需要「清潔」一下
Well, Lorraine and I both feel that what your house needs is a cleansing.
一場驅魔儀式
An exorcism.
什麼，驅魔？
What, exorcism?
我一直以為驅魔是僅針對人的
I thought that was something that you do to people.
不，不一定的
No, not necessarily, no.
我們得離開這裏
We have to get out of here.
恐怕這於事無補
I'm afraid that's not gonna help.
羅琳看到了一些…
Lorraine saw something, which--
你說吧，親愛的
Go ahead, hon.
我看到你們的房子裏有邪惡之物出沒
I've been seeing the dark entity that haunts your house...
…外面也有
...and your land.
第一次看到它是在走進你們家門的時候
I saw it first when I came through your door.
它就靠在你背上
It was latched to your back.
第二次是在走進客廳的時候，它跟女孩們在一起
And then I saw it again with the girls when we walked into the living room.
無論你們去哪裏…
And it doesn't matter where you go...
…這邪物會一直跟著你們
...this dark entity has latched itself to your family...
…吸食你們
...and it's feeding off you.
哪怕我們離開也一樣？
Even if we leave?
有時候鬼纏身，就像是踩到了口香糖
Sometimes when you get haunted,it's like stepping on gum.
會一直粘著你
You take it with you.
我得說，你們這裏有很多幽靈…
Look, I gotta tell you,you have a lot of spirits in here...
…但這個是我們最擔心的，因為它充滿了仇恨
...but this is the one that I'm most worried about, because it is so hateful.
好吧，那我們該怎麼做？叫個牧師來嗎？
Okay, so what do we do?Can we call a priest?
那麼簡單就好了
I wish it were that easy.
驅魔是一種很古老的儀式，需要很多年的訓練
Performing an exorcism is an archaic procedure. Requires years of training.
哪怕這樣，慘劇還是會時常發生
And even then,I have seen it go horribly wrong.
但在這之前，首先要獲得教堂的授權
But before we even get that far,the church has to authorize it first.
就是說我們要調查、收集證物及提供證據…
It means we gotta investigate,gather evidence and provide proof...
…這才是難點
...and that's the hard part.
孩子們受過洗禮嗎？
Have your children been baptized?
不，沒有，我們不常去教堂
Uh, no, we never got around to that.We're not really a churchgoing family.
或許應該重新考慮一下，我們的出現或許會讓事情更糟糕
Well, you may want to rethink that.Our presence here could make things worse.
為什麼？
Why?
因為我們是個威脅
Because we're a threat.
這裏這傢伙不太會喜歡我們
And whatever you're dealing with here isn't gonna like us.
目前為止它還沒施過暴，這是個好現象
So far it hasn't done anything violent,and that's a good sign.
所以我們會讓我們的人調查一下這裏…
So we're gonna have our guy do some homework on the property...
…看看我們要對付的是什麼東西
...to see what we're up against.
朱蒂，你要幹嗎？
Judy, what are you up to?
我有禮物給你
I got you a present.
我跟外婆在教堂的庭院市場上買的
Me and Nanna got these at the church's yard sale.
寶貝  - 一個給你，一個給我
Honey.  - One for you and one for me.
她在我這個裏…
She put a picture...
…放了你和爸爸的照片
...of you and Daddy in mine.
外婆說這樣我們就會永遠在一起
Nanna said this way we'll always be together.
你我會一直在一起的
You'll be with me and I'll be with you.
我想你和爸爸
I miss you and Daddy.
嗨，親愛的
Hey, hon.
在
Yup.
你不會相信的，卡洛琳的聲音沒錄下來
You're not gonna believe this.Carolyn's voice didn't record.
什麼意思？
What do you mean?
聽著
Listen.
我叫艾德·沃倫，今天是1971年11月1日
My name is Ed Warren.It's November 1st, 1971.
現在跟卡洛琳·佩倫坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正經歷著靈異事件
...who, with her family, has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，開始吧
Okay, go ahead.
從初次異常現象開始
From the first occurrence.
什麼都沒有
Nothing.
全程都是
The whole time.
不知怎麼回事，發現什麼了嗎？  - 很多
I don't know. You find anything?  - Lots.
我是說，怪不得他們會經歷這些
I mean, it's no wonder they're going through what they are.
這是之前的農場房子
That's the original farmhouse.
是1863年一個名叫傑德森·佘曼的人建造的
It was built in 1863 by a man named Jedson Sherman...
…他娶了一個名叫巴斯希巴的女人
...who was married to a woman named Bathsheba.
艾德，她是瑪麗·湯·艾斯黛的親戚
Ed, she's related to Mary Towne Estye.
是被指控在賽倫實施巫術行為的女巫之一
She was one of the women accused of witchcraft in Salem.
被判了絞刑  - 哇噢
She was hung during the trials.  - Wow.
巴斯希巴嫁給傑德森之後，生了個孩子…
After Bathsheba married Jedson,they had a baby...
…當孩子7歲的時候…
...and when the baby was 7 days old...
…傑德森發現她在壁爐邊獻祭
...Jedson caught her sacrificing it in front of the fireplace.
她跑到了碼頭那的樹邊…
She ran out to that tree by the dock...
…爬了上去，表達了對撒旦的崇拜
...climbed up, proclaimed her love to Satan...
…詛咒了每一個試圖奪走她土地的人，然後上吊自殺了
...cursed anyone who tried to take her land, and hung herself.
宣稱的死亡時間是凌晨3:07
Time of death was pronounced at 3:07 in the morning.
那一些事情就有解釋了
Well, that explains a few things.
對，還有這個
Yeah, so does this.
她姓沃克，30年代的時候住在那裏
Her last name's Walker.She lived there in the '30s.
她有個叫羅利的孩子在樹林裏神秘失蹤了
She had a boy named Rory who ysteriously disappeared in the woods.
然後她在地下室自殺了
Then she killed herself in the cellar.
這還不算完
And that's not all.
自從原本200英畝的農場被分塊賣掉之後
So, what was the original 200-acre farm as since been subdivided and sold off.
有個男孩在這個池塘裏淹死了，他住在這裏
There was another boy who drowned in pond here. He lived in a house over here.
還有一個在附近做傭人的女人，也自殺了
And a woman who worked as a maid in a eighboring home, she committed suicide too.
奪走她土地的人
People who took her land.
現在跟卡洛琳·佩倫坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正經歷著靈異事件
...who, with her family, has been xperiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，開始吧
Okay, go ahead.
從初次異常現象開始
From the first occurrence.
布拉德來了
Here's Brad.
路好找嗎？  - 是的
You find it okay?   - Oh, yeah.
德魯，這是布拉德警官
Drew, this is Officer Brad.
布拉德·漢密爾頓警官，羅德島哈瑞斯維爾警局的
Officer Brad Hamilton,Harrisville, Rhode Island P.D.
很高興見到你
Hm. Nice to meet you, man.
你是那個幸運的新警察，是嗎？  - 應該是吧
So you're the lucky new cop, huh?  - Guess so.
鬼魂用槍是打不死的，知道嗎？  - 對他友好一點，德魯
You know you can't shoot ghosts, right?  - Take it easy on him, Drew.
好了，兄弟們，幫我把這些東西搬下車
All right, guys,help me get this stuff unloaded.
你拿這個
You take this.
嗨，羅傑
Hi, Roger.
這邊好了之後，再上樓去看看，好嗎，德魯？
All right. When you're finished here,why don't you hit upstairs, all right, Drew?
知道了
You got it.
這車哪裏壞了？
What's wrong with the Chevy?
她還有哪裏是完好的嗎？
Ugh, what's not wrong with her?
需要換個新化油器才能啟動  - 是嗎？
Needs a new carburetor to start.  - Oh, yeah?
看來維修得停工一陣子了
Kind of put fixing her up on hold for a while.
嗯，是啊
Yeah. Ahem.
布拉德，把溫控器拿給我，好嗎？
Hey, Brad, hand me a thermostat,would you?
這是幹什麼用的？
What's this, uh, do?
當氣溫瞬間下降的時候…
When there's an instant drop in temperature...
…溫控器就會激發相機拍一張照片
...the thermostat triggers the camera to take a picture.
你用這玩意兒拍到過東西嗎？
You've actually caught things on film?
是的，這才是重點
Well, yeah, that's, uh, the point.
為什麼…為什麼在這裏？
Why,uh...? Why out here?
這是那女巫自殺的地方
Well, this is where the witch committed suicide.
她在你頭頂的那根樹枝上吊死了
She hung herself from that branch right above where you're standing.
為什麼母親會殺了她親生孩子？
How could a mother kill her own child?
對她來說這並不是孩子
It was never a child to her.
她只是把她當作工具來攻擊上帝
She just used her God-given gift as the ultimate offense against him.
女巫們相信撒旦可以提升她們的能力
Witches believe it elevates their status in the eyes of Satan.
那天在海灘玩得很開心，是吧？
Wow.That's a nice day at the beach, huh?
你怎麼知道的？
How did you know?
這是一種能力，就像是透過窗簾窺視別人的生活一樣
It's an insight. It's like a peek through the curtain into another person's life.
那一天對我意義非凡，我們正沿著海岸開車
That day meant so much to me.We were driving along the coast.
南希說那裏很漂亮
Nancy pointed out how pretty the view was.
我想這是個拍照的好時機
I thought this is a perfect opportunity for a photo.
我們正打算重新開始，新的房子，新的起點
We're gonna start fresh, you know?A new house, a new beginning.
你也見過羅傑跟姑娘們了，我從沒見他們那麼開心過
You should have seen Roger and the girls.I've never seen them so happy.
茄子！
Cheese!
他們對我來說就是一切
They mean the world to me.
把你的手平放在桌子上
Put your hand flat on the desk.
好，然後拿開
Yeah, and take it off.
開始了
Here we go.
看到了嗎？
See?
這能讓我們看到那些肉眼看不到的東西
It just reveals to us what the naked eye can't see.
高科技，是吧？
Pretty far out, isn't it?
是啊，好神奇
Yeah, it's groovy.
德魯，布拉德的攝像機準備好了嗎？
Drew, you got the Bolex ready for Brad?
是的，一切就緒，先生
Yeah, already locked and loaded, sir.
怎麼了？人有三急嘛
What? I had to go.
所有房間信號正常
All the rooms are coming in pretty good.
很好
Good.
瓶子裏是什麼？
What's in the bottle?
聖水
Holy water.
像這樣的宗教信物…
Presence of religious icons...
…會讓任何邪惡的東西起反應
...will get a reaction from anything unholy.
類似於激怒他們
Sort of pisses them off.
所以我滿屋子都放了這些，看能不能佔據點優勢
So I set these throughout the house,see if I can stir things up a bit.
就像對著吸血鬼亮出十字架？  - 對，沒錯
Like holding a cross to a vampire?  - Yeah. Exactly.
除了我不相信有吸血鬼之外
Except I don't believe in vampires.
不是我
Wasn't me.
布拉德，拿上攝像機
Brad, get the camera.
好了
Okay.
現在是晚上9:18，我們準備進入地下室，剛才那裏的門自己開了
All right, it's 9:18, we're headed down into the cellar where the door's just opened on its own.
羅琳跟布拉德警官跟我一起
I have Lorraine and Officer Brad Hamilton with me.
地下室的燈保持關閉
Let's keep the cellar light off.
如果想跟我們交流，就給我們點提示吧
Give us a sign that you wanna communicate with us.
親愛的，你還好嗎？
Hon, you all right?
這裏肯定有什麼東西
There's definitely something here.
關個門，移動點東西什麼的  - 我的手很冷
All right, close the door. Move something.  - My hands are so cold.
來啊
Come on.
不
No.
它走了，它走了
It's gone. It's gone.
我什麼都沒錄到
I got nothing.
好的
Okay.
就像我說的，並不是每次都能如願以償
Well, like I said, it doesn't always work when you want it to.
是啊，也許攝像機拍到了點什麼
Yeah, maybe the camera picked something up.
小心！
Watch out!
作為無神論者…
For a guy who doesn't believe...
…門摔上的時候你們好像嚇傻了嘛
...you looked a little freaked out when that door slammed shut.
肯定是風
It must have been a draft.
噢，滑稽
Oh, that's funny.
風從來不會讓我出現那種表情
A draft never put that look on my face before.
我更相信那鍾
I believe the clock.
3:08了
It's 3:08.
給我看看你的眼鏡
Let me see your glasses.
給你的
For you.
待會兒我想帶幾個女孩子去吃冰激淋，覺得怎麼樣？
I think I might take some girls for ice cream later on. What do you say about that?
好的！  - 親愛的，一起嗎？
Yeah!  - Honey, you wanna come?
我累死了，我要睡一會兒，好困
I'm exhausted. I'm just gonna take a nap.The late nights are getting to me.
好主意，你休息一會兒吧
That's probably a good idea.Why don't you get some rest.
羅琳和我會照看這裏  - 真的嗎？
Lorraine and I'll watch over things for a bit.  - Really?
我要出發了，一小時後我有活
I'm gonna take off.I have a shift starting in an hour.
這個家很久都沒有這樣了
The house hasn't felt like this in a long time.
有你們在，孩子們有安全感多了
I think the kids feel a lot safer with you around.
我會習慣起來的  - 什麼？我洗衣服？
I could get used to this.  - What, me doing laundry?
你真幽默
You're funny.
這地方…
No, this place.
漂亮，新鮮的鄉村空氣
Nice, fresh country air.
他們有個很幸福的家，是吧？
They have such a beautiful family,don't they?
是啊，那小傢伙，艾普麗爾，有沒有看到她給我拿煎餅？
Yeah, that little one, April,did you see her bring me pancakes?
是的
Yeah!
我們得幫他們
We've gotta help them.
我知道
I know.
從修好那輛車開始
I'll start with the Chevy.
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
卡洛琳，開門
Carolyn, open the door.
卡洛琳，快開門！
Carolyn, open up!
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
我沒事  - 你病了嗎？
Oh, I'm fine.  - Are you sick?
我醒過來感覺有點想吐，僅此而已  - 我看到了…
I woke up feeling nauseous, that's all.  - I thought I saw...
我聽到羅傑跟孩子們回來了
I hear Roger and the girls.
稍等
One minute.
姐妹們，想玩遊戲嗎？  - 無聊！
Guys, do you wanna play a game?  - Boring!
謝謝，爸爸
Thank you, Daddy.
我們進去吧
Let's go inside.
就知道是你
I thought that was you.
希望你不要介意
Hey, I hope you don't mind.
我在史密斯菲爾德的廢車場低價買了個拆車件
I got a good deal on a rebuild at that wrecking yard in Smithfield.
不，你看起來很精通啊  - 是的，瞧我的
No, you look like you know what you're doing.  - Yeah, we'll see.
這地方不錯，羅傑
Got a nice place here, Roger.
羅琳跟我一直想在鄉下買套房子
Lorraine and I always wanted a spot in the country.
我把這裏賣給你吧
I'll sell you this one.
把扳手遞給我
Hey, hand me a wrench, would you?
嗨，你們能來這裏，真是感激不盡
Hey, uh, it really means a lot to us to have you here.
我承認，之前我是有點不相信這些
I gotta admit, I was a little bit skeptical going in.
就想說一聲謝謝，對於你們所做的一切
Just wanna say thank you, though,for coming out when you did.
我不能接受這份謝意，這都是羅琳的功勞
I can't take the credit.That's, uh... That's all Lorraine.
我並不想這麼做  - 為什麼？
I didn't want to.  - Oh. Why's that?
羅琳所看到的、感受到的、接觸到的，可以幫助別人
Whatever Lorraine sees, feels, touches,it helps people.
但同時也會給她帶來傷害
But it also takes a toll on her.
每次一點點
Little piece each time.
幾個月前，我們正在處理一個案子
Couple months ago we were working on a case.
她看到了一些東西
She saw something.
造成了很大的傷害
It took a real big piece.
我們回家後…
When we got home...
…她進了房間，把自己鎖在了裏面…
...she went into our room,locked herself in...
…整整八天，不說，不吃，不出門
...didn't talk, didn't eat,didn't come out for eight days.
她看到了什麼？
What'd she see?
出去！
Get out of here!
不知道
I don't know.
我也不會問
And I won't ask.
我要再去倒一杯，你要嗎？
I need to reload. You want some?
不用，謝謝
I'm good, thanks.
好吧
All right.
看看她都讓我幹了些什麼
Look what she made me do.
嗨
Hey.
艾德？
Ed?
看看她都讓我幹了些什麼
Look what she made me do!
艾德！艾德！
Ed! Ed!
艾德！
Ed!
哥們兒，你還好嗎？
Dude, you okay?
冷靜點，布拉德，怎麼了？
Hold up, Brad. What's going on?
我看到了一個穿著傭人服的女人
I saw someone. There was a woman dressed as a maid.
艾德？艾德，有情況
Ed? Ed, we're getting something.
是辛蒂，她在夢遊  - 不，等等
It's just Cindy. She's sleepwalking.  - No, wait. We need this.
為什麼要給辛蒂拍照？
Why do we need pictures of Cindy?
不是她激發的
She didn't trigger it.
不是她激發的？什麼意思？  - 有人跟她在一起
What do you mean she didn't trigger it?  - Somebody's with her.
誰？
Who?
辛蒂！
Cindy!
過來這裏，這裏安全
Hey, over here. It's safe.
有人跟她在一起
There's someone else in there with her.
我聽到了另一個聲音，這裏，聽
I'm hearing another voice. Here, listen.
跟我來，這邊走
Follow me. This way.
這就是我躲的地方
This is where I hide.
辛蒂？
Cindy?
她去哪裏了，艾德？
Where'd she go, Ed?
窗子都鎖上了
Windows are locked.
艾德，她去哪裏了？
Ed, where'd she go?
布拉德，把紫外燈拿來
Brad, get the UV light.
什麼？  - 問德魯
The what?  - Just ask Drew.
德魯，我要個紫外燈
Drew, I need a UV light.
給，就這個，快去，快去！
Here, that's it. Go, go, go, go!
關燈
Turn off the light.
讓開
Get out of the way.
好的
Okay.
開燈！
Hit the lights!
找到她了
Found her.
過來吧
Here we go.
抱好了？  - 是的
All right. You got her?  - Yeah.
那就是羅利害怕的時候躲的地方
That's where Rory hides when he's afraid.
親愛的？把艾普麗爾的音樂盒給我
Hon? Could I have April's music box, please?
辛蒂怎麼樣？  - 她什麼都不記得
How's Cindy?  - She doesn't remember a thing.
給你
Here you go.
謝謝
Thank you.
羅琳！
Lorraine!
不
No.
羅琳！
Lorraine!
是她讓我這麼做的
She made me do it.
艾德！
Ed!
拜託！羅琳！
Come on! Lorraine!
艾德！
Ed!
艾德，我知道她做了什麼
Ed, I know what she did.
我扶你，我知道，沒事了  - 我知道她做了什麼
I got you. I know. It's okay.  - I know what she did.
我知道她做了什麼，她附身在那媽媽身上殺了那孩子
I know what she did. She possessed the mother to kill the child.
她每晚都會去卡洛琳那裏
She visits Carolyn every night.
所以才會有那些淤青！她在吸食她！
That's what the bruise marks are!She's feeding off of her!
呃…
Uh....
南希？
Nancy?
南希！
Nancy!
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
南希！
Nancy!
抓住她！
Grab her!
爸爸！救命！
Daddy! Help!
南希！
Nancy!
她還好嗎？
Is she okay?
沒事了，沒事了
It's okay, I got you.
拍到了嗎？
Did you get that?
是的
Yeah.
我去沖印膠片，然後拿給哥頓神父
I'll have the footage developed and get it over to Father Gordon.
他是我們教堂方面的聯絡人，我們會很快得到回應的
He's our liaison at the church.I imagine we'll get a pretty fast response.
聽著，羅傑？  - 什麼？
Listen, Roger?  - Yeah?
聽著，我們接到驅魔人就會回來，但羅琳…
Listen, when we get the exorcist,I'll be back. But Lorraine--
是的，我明白  - 在這之前，德魯會照看你們的
Yeah, I understand.  - Until then Drew's gonna keep an eye on you.
艾德，感謝你所做的一切  - 嗯
Hey, Ed, thank you for everything.  - Yeah.
媽咪？
Mommy?
就這些了
That's everything.
媽咪？
Mommy?
朱蒂？
Judy?
噢，上帝啊！
Oh, God!
朱蒂？
Judy?
羅琳！等等！
Lorraine! Wait!
羅琳，怎麼了？
Lorraine. What?
媽媽，是我，朱蒂還好嗎？
Mom, it's me. Is Judy okay?
什麼？  - 可以去看一下嗎？
What?  - Can you go check, please?
該死的，媽媽，去看一下就是了！
Damn it, Mom, just check, please!
可以告訴我到底怎麼了嗎？  - 是朱蒂
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?  - It's Judy.
什麼？什麼意思？
What? What do you mean?
什麼意思？
What?
噢，謝天謝地
Oh, thank God.
媽媽，對不起，我不是有意要嚇你的，回頭再跟你解釋
Mom, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you. I'll explain later, okay?
這他媽到底怎麼回事？
What the hell happened?
我看到朱蒂在湖裏
I had a vision of Judy in the water.
我知道這是某種警告
I know it was some kind of warning.
我知道的
I know it.
好了
Okay.
我們走吧
Let's get out of here.
然後？  - 嗯，你們不是開玩笑
So?  - Yeah, well, you weren't kidding.
是的
No.
艾德，這事有點複雜，因為那些孩子們沒有經過洗禮
Look, Ed, this is complicated because the kids aren't baptized.
是的，我理解  - 那家人也不是教會成員
No, I understand.  - And the family are not members of the church.
噢，拜託  - 還有…
Oh, come on.  - And....
許可令必須由梵蒂岡直接下發
The approval would have to come directly from the Vatican.
神父，我們從沒見過這樣的東西
Father, we've never seen nothing like this.
是的，我也沒見過
Yeah, well, neither have l.
神父，他們沒那麼多時間了
Father, they don't have a lot of time.
好吧
All right.
我會親自跟進這事的
I'll push it through myself.
謝謝，神父，謝謝  - 謝謝
Thank you, Father. Thank you.  - Thank you.
我們等你電話  - 好的
All right, we'll wait for your call.  - Yeah.
媽媽？爸爸？
Mommy? Daddy?
媽媽？
Mommy?
爸爸？
Daddy?
Dad?
外婆？
Nanna?
外婆！
Nanna!
外婆，救命！外婆，救命！
Nanna, help! Nanna, help!
朱蒂？
Judy?
外婆！
Nanna!
救命！
Help!
朱蒂！  - 外婆！
Judy!  - Nanna!
朱蒂，開門！  - 媽媽！
Judy, open the door!  - Mom!
艾德，有點不對勁  - 什麼？
Ed, there's something wrong.  - What?
外婆！
Nanna!
朱蒂！  - 救命！
Judy!  - Help!
朱蒂！朱蒂，開門！  - 怎麼了？
Judy! Judy, open this door!  - What is it?
她怎麼了？朱蒂！  - 讓開，讓開，讓開，讓開
What's wrong with her? Judy!  - Hey, move. Move, move, move, move.
朱蒂，退後，寶貝，退後
Judy, get back, honey. Get back!
拜託！  - 快點
Come on!  - Hurry.
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
離門遠一點，朱蒂！
Get away from the door, Judy!
噢，上帝！你沒事吧？
Oh, God! Are you okay?
有個人在跟安娜貝爾一起搖椅子
There was someone rocking in the chair with Annabelle.
什麼？
What?
沒事了
It's okay.
她還在箱子裏
She's still in the case.
沒事了
It's okay.
沒事了，沒事了
It's okay. It's okay.
爸爸！爸爸！  - 爸爸！
Dad! Dad!  - Daddy!
爸爸！爸爸！媽媽帶著克裏斯蒂和艾普麗爾走了
Dad! Dad! Mom just left with Christine and April.
她進了車子然後開走了，我不知道發生了什麼事
She went in the car and drove away.I don't know what happened.
她聞起來有股爛肉味道  - 她沒說到底是怎麼了
She smells like rotting meat.  - She didn't say what was going on.
她走了是什麼意思？走去哪了？  - 就是走了！不知道去哪裏了
What do you mean, she left? Left where?  - Gone! I don't know where she was going.
我們去哪，媽媽？
Where are we going, Mom?
喂？  - 我是羅傑
Hello?  - It's Roger.
有事發生在卡洛琳身上了
Something's going on with Carolyn.
安德莉亞在，她說卡洛琳帶著克裏斯蒂和艾普麗爾走了
Andrea was here,said Carolyn took off with Christine and April.
孩子們說她聞起來像塊爛肉  - 附身於母親…
The girls said she smelled like rotten meat.  - Possesses the mother...
…來殺掉孩子，她就是這麼做的，她要把她們帶去那房子
...to kill the child, that's what she does.She's taking them to the house.
羅傑，現在去房子裏，我在那跟你碰頭
Roger, get back to the house now.I'll meet you there.
鎖上門，拉上窗簾，遠離電話
Lock the door, close the blinds.Stay off the phone!
走
Go.
我跟你一起去  - 不行，你陪著朱蒂
I'm coming with you.  - Noway, you stay with Judy.
保護朱蒂的唯一辦法就是終結這一切
Only way to protect Judy is if we stop this where it started.
否則她會再次纏上我們  - 這正是我要去做的
Otherwise, she'll latch onto us again.  - That's exactly why I am going.
你覺得我會讓你一個人去嗎？
You think I'm gonna let you walk into this alone?
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
你不會的
You won't.
我們一起把這事終結吧
Let's finish this together.
鎖上了  - 卡洛琳！
Agh! It's locked.  - Carolyn!
羅傑！
Roger!
讓開！
Get out of the way!
羅傑！  - 艾德！
Roger!  - Ed!
卡洛琳！  - 艾德！
Carolyn!  - Ed!
卡洛琳！  - 我們在這裏！
Carolyn!  - We're down here!
卡洛琳，不要！不，不！她抓著…！
Carolyn, don't!No, no! She's got...!
抓住她手！把剪刀奪下來！
Get her hand! Get the scissors!
我們得把她帶到車裏！  - 然後把她帶去哪？
We gotta get her to the car!  - And bring her where?
把她帶到神父那裏驅魔
To take her to the priest for the exorcism.
艾普麗爾在哪？  - 艾普麗爾？
Where's April?  - April?
艾普麗爾！
April!
把克裏斯蒂帶上車，把艾普麗爾找出來！
Take Christine to the car and find April!
艾普麗爾！
April!
趕緊！
Come on!
她不讓她離開這房子  - 什麼意思？
She won't let her leave the house.  - What do you mean?
如果把她帶出來，女巫會殺了她的
If we take her out, the witch will kill her.
羅傑！
Roger!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
快去！
Go!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn?
我把你放在這裏，來
Okay, I'm gonna put you in here.Come on.
進去，呆裏面  - 我不想一個人在這裏
Get in. Stay in here.  - I don't wanna stay here by myself.
呆在這裏，我很快回來
Stay in here no matter what.I'll be back.
我要去找艾普麗爾，知道嗎？很快回來，我發誓
I have to find April, okay?I'll be back, I promise.
艾普麗爾？
April?
你沒事吧？
You okay?
住手！
Stop!
布拉德！布拉德！
Brad! Brad!
找點什麼東西把她綁起來
Let's get something to tie her up!
按住
Hold it.
我得打電話把哥頓神父叫過來
I gotta call Father Gordon.We gotta get him out here.
他離的太遠了，她撐不了那麼久，看看她
He's too far away.She won't make it. Look at her.
那你得離開了  - 你在說什麼？
Then you need to leave.  - What are you talking about?
我得進行驅魔儀式
I have to do it. The exorcism.
什麼？你不是說需要一個神父嗎，你又不是神父
What? I thought you said we need a priest. You're not a priest.
你有更好的主意？  - 他可以的
Well, you got a better idea?  - He can do it.
你可以的  - 但你得離開這裏
You can do it.  - But you gotta get out of here.
我不會離開你！  - 該死的，你不能在這裏！
I'm not leaving you!  - Damn it, I'm not doing this with you in here!
上帝把我們撮合在一起是有原因的，就這樣
God brought us together for a reason.This is it.
我去拿書
I'm gonna get the book.
艾普麗爾！
April!
「以吾聖父，聖子，聖靈之名」
"In the name of the Father,the Son, the Holy Spirit."
艾普麗爾！
April!
按住她！按住她！
Hold her still! Hold her still!
過來！按住她！
Come here! Hold her still!
艾普麗爾？
April?
艾普麗爾！
April!
艾普麗爾，你在下面嗎？
April, you under there?
艾普麗爾！
April!
卡洛琳，卡洛琳，別放棄！別讓她佔有你！
Carolyn. Carolyn. Don't give in!Don't let her take you!
艾德！不能再繼續了，你會殺了她的，住手！
Ed! You gotta stop,you're killing her. Stop!
不，不能停！
No, he can't!
羅傑，救我！
Roger, help me!
艾德！該死的，住手！
Ed! Goddamn it, stop it!
記住！我們是在為她的靈魂做鬥爭！
Understand this! We are now fighting for her soul!
「以耶穌基督、聖人、天使之名…
"In the name of Jesus Christ,the saints and all the angels...
…我命令你揭開你的真面目！」
...I command you to reveal yourself!"
羅傑，救我！
Roger, help me!
放她下來！
Put her down!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
艾德，小心！
Ed, look out!
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
按住她！別讓她再上去！
Hold her still! Don't let her up!
她快不行了，羅傑！
We're losing her, Roger!
去你的！離我家人遠點，聽到沒有？
Damn you! You leave my family alone,you hear me?
我不知道你是誰，但離我妻子遠一點，該死的！
I don't know what you are, but you leave my wife alone, goddamn it!
放開她！聽到沒？放開她！
Let her go!Do you hear me? Let her go!
放開她，該死的！放開她！
Let her go, goddamn it! Let her go!
她已經死了
She's already gone.
現在你們都得死
And now you're all gonna die.
艾普麗爾！
April!
找到她了！她在下面！廚房下面！
I found her! She's under the house!Under the kitchen!
不要！不！
Don't! No!
抓住她！
Get her!
給  - 卡洛琳！
Here.  - Carolyn!
卡洛琳！  - 她在那洞裏，就在那裏
Carolyn!  - She's in that hole. Right there.
卡洛琳？上帝啊，不！
Carolyn? Oh, my God. No!
進不去，夠不到
Can't go in. Can't reach.
不！卡洛琳，不要！
No! Carolyn, don't!
卡洛琳，不要！
Carolyn, no!
巴斯希巴！
Bathsheba!
吾借上帝之力，命汝重回地獄！
By the power of God,I condemn you back to hell!
這是你女兒！
This is your daughter!
你不能屈服
You can't give in!
羅傑，我們得讓她自己反抗
Roger. We need to get her to fight from the inside.
別讓她這麼做，別讓那東西這麼做！
Don't let her do this.Don't let this thing do this.
你要反抗，我知道你比她更強
You gotta fight it.I know you're stronger than she is.
你要跟它抗爭！  - 繼續，羅傑！
You gotta fight it!  - Keep it going, Roger!
別離開我們，好嗎？回來，卡洛琳！
You gotta stay with us, all right?Come on back, Carolyn!
對了，就這樣！帶她回來！
You're in, that's it! Get her back!
想一想你給我看的照片  - 不！
Remember what you showed me.  - No!
想一想你說的那永世難忘的一天
Remember that day that you said you would never forget.
你說他們就是你的一切
You said they meant the world to you.
這些你都不要了嗎？
This is what you'll be leaving behind.
媽媽？
Mommy?
都結束了
It's over.
真對不起
I am so sorry.
愛死你了，愛死你了
I love you so much. I love you so much.
愛死你了
I love you so much.
我太高興了
I'm so happy.
是風把你臉弄成這樣的嗎？
A draft do that to your face?
我寧願每天都面對持槍歹徒
I'd take a guy with a gun any day.
你做的很好
You did good.
不，你才是
No, you did.
我打個電話給哥頓神父，告訴他這一切
I'll call Father Gordon and let him know what happened.
聽起來不錯
Sounds good.
梵蒂岡批准了驅魔儀式
The Vatican approved the exorcism.
來的真是時候
Heh. Nice timing.
還有如果可以的話，他明天想見見我們
And if we can, then he'd like to meet with us tomorrow.
長島有一個案子，他想跟我們討論一下
There's a case in Long Island he'd like to discuss.
是嗎？
Really?
「邪惡力量非常強大，至今一直存在著。這故事是真實的，惡魔和上帝確實存在。
對我們凡人而言，我們的命運取決於選擇站在哪一邊。」
- 艾德·沃倫
*佩倫一家*
*沃倫一家*
貓妖先生@CHDBits原創翻譯&校對
*感謝觀影*